
<speak xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis"
    xmlns:mstts="http://www.w3.org/2001/mstts"
    xmlns:emo="http://www.w3.org/2009/10/emotionml" version="1.0" xml:lang="en-US">






<voice name="en-US-GuyNeural"><mstts:express-as style="newscast" ><prosody rate="7%" pitch="0%" volume="60">This is parser</prosody></mstts:express-as></voice>
<voice name="en-US-AmberNeural"><prosody rate="3%" pitch="-7%" volume="60">A podcast about the first 100 years of the internet</prosody></voice>
<voice name="en-US-JennyNeural"><break time="100ms" /></voice>
<voice name="en-US-GuyNeural"><mstts:express-as style="newscast" ><prosody rate="7%" pitch="0%" volume="60">In todays episode we set the ground for season one and you get to know who we are.</prosody></mstts:express-as></voice>
<voice name="en-US-JennyNeural"><break time="100ms" /></voice>
<voice name="en-US-JennyNeural"><break time="100ms" /></voice>
<voice name="en-US-AmberNeural"><prosody rate="3%" pitch="-7%" volume="60">Once you start to learn a programming language you usually do an exercice that's called 'Hello World'. And this is probably our own «Hello World» warm up in front of a bigger audience. But hey John! Please explain to me what it is for you?</prosody></voice>
<voice name="en-US-GuyNeural"><mstts:express-as style="newscast" ><prosody rate="7%" pitch="0%" volume="60">oh gosh... Where to start? For me it's probably a format where I have a chance to hear storys of a recent history. But I would like to forward that question to our producer. Take it away Stefan.</prosody></mstts:express-as></voice>
<voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural"><prosody rate="0%" pitch="-2%" volume="60">Thank you John and Sara. We plan to produce a podcast where we put a spotlight on the recent history of computers. We wrap historical facts about commmunicating technology. In short episodes we talk about the history to hopefully understand the future.</prosody></voice>
<voice name="en-US-AmberNeural"><prosody rate="3%" pitch="-7%" volume="60">The parser is a computer generated podcast that is written in text and output for you as audio.</prosody></voice>
<voice name="en-US-GuyNeural"><mstts:express-as style="newscast" ><prosody rate="7%" pitch="0%" volume="60">If you like the format, hear mistakes or have suggestions for improvement, please visit our website and comment. We understand the format in an itterative way.</prosody></mstts:express-as></voice>
<voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural"><prosody rate="0%" pitch="-2%" volume="60">Starting in 2022 you will get season one about the first steps of sounds on the internet. Stay tuned.</prosody></voice>
<voice name="en-US-JennyNeural"><break time="100ms" /></voice>






</speak>